Yo, what's going on everybody? Laura
Tech here with another video and today I
have a pretty cool workflow for you
guys. What this workflow aims to do is
create Instagram carousels which if you
guys haven't heard the word around town,
Instagram carousels are kind of becoming
the meta of Instagram at least for AI
influencers.
Um, especially because just how easy
they are to make. So,
what we're going to be doing today is
taking a reference image
which can also use Laura support if you
have a Flux 2 client Laura trained. If
not, no big deal. You don't really need
it for this workflow. Will it increase
the likeness? Yes, of course it it
always will. So, I do recommend training
a Flux 2 Laura.
You can you can train a Flux 2 Laura the
same way that I trained my Z image turbo
Laura in my previous video which you can
find on my profile. You guys know where
all the uh references that I'll be using
for this video are going to be just
right on my profile. So, if you need to
check out something that references a
previous video or something like that,
just go check out the YouTube page.
It'll it'll be all in there. So, let's
get started with the workflow. I'm just
going to run you guys through it real
quick. So, yes, this is a Flux 2 client
9B
uh workflow that's that's the model that
it's using. So, I know I swear by Z
image turbo and I still use Z image
turbo. It's my favorite model. But for
image editing, Flux 2 client is just
unbeatable right now. I mean it it's
it's it's great and the generations are
lightning fast. So, you really just
can't beat it. So, our main diffusion
model is going to be Flux 2 client 9
billion parameters.
Our VAE is going to be the Flux 2 VAE
obviously and our clip is going to be
the Quinn 3 8 billion parameter clip.
So, make sure you guys get those
installed. If you don't know how to
install models onto your
whatever you're using for ComfyUI
whether it be RunPod or a local ComfyUI,
this probably isn't the video for you. I
have tons of videos explaining how to do
that in every single video. So, go back
and catch up. You got a little bit of
learning to do. I'm just going to get
right down to the workflow.
So,
this is a carousel builder for
specifically a reference image. So, you
can see here I have Master Chief. What's
up, Master Chief? You got a full body
image here, Mr. Master Chief. Looking
great. And down here, what you'll need
to pay attention to are these two prompt
lists that we have here. Now, you'll
notice one one prompt list is named full
body prompt list. So, this is for images
obviously that include the full body of
the reference character that you're
using. So, in my example,
I am using a full body reference image
of Master Chief. So, I'm going to use
this prompt list. Now,
let's say you have a selfie for example.
Um, just a different type of photo that
you may commonly use as a reference
image. That is completely fine. I have
obviously in the full body prompt list
here, a bunch of slightly varying full
body prompts that will get different
angles, different poses.
You don't have to change anything here.
This is all already set up exactly
for how you're going to need it if you
just want to get like very similar
images with similar backgrounds and
similar clothing, just different poses,
you know, like something that you would
see on an Instagram carousel. Now, if
you are using a selfie, all you have to
do here is very simple. Just press
control B to bypass the full body prompt
list and then come over to the selfie
prompt list here. Press control B on
that to enable it. Now, if you do end up
changing anything and deleting stuff in
here, deleted by accident or whatever
might happen, I have them down in a text
box here for you to copy that copy and
paste back in there. So, they're right
down there for you if you want to just
go back to default.
So, once you enable the selfie prompt
list if you're using a selfie, all you
need to do is take the prompt output of
this prompt list and drag it into the
text box of the positive prompt box
here.
You don't want to drag it in the clip.
It just won't go in there. You it just
goes into the text box.
So, that's what you do if you're using a
selfie and then if you're switching back
and forth, you know, just control B,
turn the selfie one off and come back to
the full body and
enable it and just drag that prompt node
or prompt wiring into the text box of
the positive prompt there.
So,
if you are wanting to change the size of
the image here, what this is going to
look like by default is something like
this.
Taking the width and the height of our
reference image
and just putting it into this Flux 2
latent basically image resizer here.
This is what determines the dimensions
of the picture.
But, you'll see here I'm using a
gigantic image. I don't know why this
picture of Master Chief is so [__]
big, but it's massive. 3155 by 3155.
That's huge. But, what we do know about
this image is that it is one to one. The
dimensions are the same. So, all I have
to really do to
get a similar output is bypass this
get image node here and then remove the
wiring from the width and the height in
this Flux 2 latent node. And now you you
see here that you should be able to do
specify the
width and height that you want.
One thing I'm going to say about this
though is that you do not want to
change the the um what do you call it?
The resolution. So, if it if it's let's
say it's a one to one image just like
mine is. We have 3155 height by 3155
width. I'm going to be I'm going to do
1024 width by 1024 height. It's still
one to one. Nothing's really changing.
It's just making the image smaller. What
you don't want to do is take a one to
one image and change it to something
like nine to 16. It's going to look
smushed and [__] up and you just don't
want to do that. So, don't do that. But,
you can find out the dimensions of your
reference image pretty easily. Basic
math or ask an LLM, they'll do the math
for you.
One thing before we run the workflow is
obviously yes, guys, we have our face
detailer and eye detailer. These are a
core part of my workflows. I always put
them in everything.
For things like Master Chief though,
like I don't want to detail the face
because he doesn't have a face
obviously. He wears a he wears a [__]
mask. So,
what I'm going to do here is just bypass
these nodes
because I don't want to detail any of
that stuff cuz it's just going to make
it look not right. It's going to make
him actually have a face most likely.
So, I don't want that.
If you don't know how to use the face
detailer and eye detailer and you want
to use them, again, head over to another
one of my videos. I use them in every
single workflow and all you have to do
is install like a really small it's like
a
75 megabyte model and it gives you
insane results for just face detail and
eye detail, everything about the face.
It's great. So, I do recommend using
these if you're using something that has
a face, but we're not. So, I'm going to
run this workflow now. I've pretty much
gone through everything and I'm just
going to show you how crazy this is and
how much the image stays the same while
just changing the character.
While this generates, I do just want to
point one thing out as well here is that
if you do have a Flux 2 client Laura
trained, um you can go ahead and just
put your Laura right into this uh Laura
loader stack here. You just pick it and
put it in there. If you don't, no harm,
no foul. You can just bypass this if you
want. Control B on it. If you don't want
to use a Laura, that's completely fine.
This workflow is designed to work
perfectly fine without a Laura. You will
get pretty damn consistent generations
with just a good reference image. Just
make sure that the face is obviously
visible or it's going to imagine a
random face for every generation.
Make sure that the face isn't too far
away or it's going to guess things like
eye color because it's too far away for
it to actually get a good reference of
it. So, yeah, just wanted to point that
out.
One last thing to point out also, if you
want to change the steps in the sampler
here, uh what you're not going to do is
change the steps in the sampler. I know,
sounds weird. What you're going to do is
change the steps in the speed of
sampling scheduler here. I use this in a
lot of my workflows as well. This is
another one of the things that I always
use. It's um
I'll explain it probably in depth in
another video when it's more relevant,
but for now, you just change the steps
here if you want more steps in your
generations.
All right, my generations are done. So,
here we go. Um, I know it's funny I said
turn off the face detailer because I
don't want him to have a face, but
sometimes
[__] happens, I guess.
The the point of this workflow really is
that you're you're generating 10 10
images per run of this workflow. So,
you're not obviously not going to use 10
images to upload to Instagram for your
carousel. But, what you can use are the
ones that are good. So,
you can see here that we just have
Master Chief chilling. Got the no
smoking sign back there in the
background and it's consistent in every
single image. I mean, everything is
pretty much the exact same. Just he
changes. We have him sitting down here.
That's pretty awesome. So, I mean,
that's pretty much it for the workflow,
guys. Like I said, if you're using a
selfie, just do the thing with the
prompt boxes that I said. Don't go
[__] around with the any other
settings if you don't really know what
any of them do. You're probably just
going to ruin the workflow and then have
to uh re-drag it into your ComfyUI from
scratch. So, yeah. If you don't know
what anything does, don't [__] with it
and um I'm going to wrap this video up.
Um, I feel like I did a good job
explaining it and just
showing you guys what the workflow does.
So, if you want this workflow, you will
be able to find it in my Discord. It's
completely free. It'll be in the free
workflow section in my Discord. And
final reminder for the last reminder for
the video, if uh
you have never used RunPod before
and you want to get into AI image
generation, just go to my profile, go to
my YouTube page. I have videos from the
scratch that will teach you how to do
everything from scratch, from the very
first
typing runpod.io into your URL bar for
the first time. I have videos for it.
So, go check that out if you're new and
you want to do stuff like this. And
thank you for watching.